Dr.Ryan Lazo

Phone: (505) 907-4414 E-Mail: ryanlazo12@gmail.com

I spent the last 5 years working in the medical industry as a Chiropractor before a chance encounter turned me on to the world of Software Development. In my time as a Chiropractor I gained valuable experience working as a member of a team and coordinating with patients to solve unique, specialized problems. My willingness to learn, determination to become a productive employee, and flexible attitude make me a unique asset to any team. Though I specialize in medical tech, I have a passion for all things programming and my experience in the workforce has made me a versatile professional able to adapt to a variety of complicated situations.

Experience

Deep Dive Coding

2018-present

Experience using Java, Android, Salesforce, Jshell, Github, SQL, HTML, CSS, Javadoc.

Gonstead Physical Medicine

2016-2018

I am a practicing chiropractor at Gonstead Physical Medicine. My responsibilities include direct patient care, performing and reading technical reports, medical documentation, working with vendor management, and developing patient care plans based on their needs.

New Mexico Back Institute

2008-2010

I was the primary spinal decompression technician and patient care plan coordinator. Organized social media and public service events. I was also the head of customer support and computer troubleshooting.

Education

Palmer College of Chiropractic

2013-2016

Graduated with a degree in Chiropractic and a Masters Degree in Human Sciences. While in school I received several certifications and I was nominated for the clinical excellence award.

University of New Mexico

2008-2012

I was awarded a Bachelor's Degree in Marketing/Communications with a minor Psychology.